{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/4023","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4023","name":"Albano Coney Island/DBA Apollo","address":"7635 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48204","owner":"Zef Gega","licenseNumber":"066448","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.11435,42.35839","geojson":{"id":"4023","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.11435421,42.358386083]},"properties":{"name":"Albano Coney Island/DBA Apollo","owner":"Zef Gega","address":"7635 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48204","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"066448","establishmentid":"4023","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"2023-04-14"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1346","name":"Ed's Apollo's Coney Island","address":"7635 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"314","name":"Little Mary's River Inn","address":"7741 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"602","name":"Louie's Cocktail Lounge","address":"8053 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"5225","name":"Harlem Fresh Fish & Chicken LLC","address":"7320 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"4129","name":"J & J Fish & Chicken","address":"7320 Grand River Ave.","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"1434","name":"High School For Performing Arts","address":"4333 Rosa Parks","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"4885","name":"New Center Community Health","address":"2051 Grand Blvd. W.","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"922","name":"Sampson/Webber Academy","address":"4700 Tireman","zipcode":"48204"},{"establishmentid":"1256","name":"Wingert Trainable Center","address":"1851 Grand Blvd. W.","zipcode":"48208"},{"establishmentid":"3534","name":"Westside Alternative High School","address":"1851 Grand Blvd. W.","zipcode":"48208"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"61511","inspectionDate":"2022-10-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-11-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"57673","inspectionDate":"2022-03-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2022-03-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Above the ACCESS","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"55823","inspectionDate":"2021-09-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Commercially processed ready to eat potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-09-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"GRILL AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2021-09-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"52777","inspectionDate":"2020-09-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-09-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"51565","inspectionDate":"2020-04-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19/phone-high","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"49113","inspectionDate":"2019-09-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"SLICER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall only contact surfaces of EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS that are cleaned and SANITIZED, or SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not properly cleaned and sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"7-202.12","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS shall be:    \n(A) Used according to:      \n(1) LAW and this Code,   \n(2) Manufacturer's use directions included in labeling, and, for a pesticide, manufacturer's label instructions that state that use is allowed in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, (P)   \n(3) The conditions of certification, if certification is required, for use of the pest control materials, (P) and   \n(4) Additional conditions that may be established by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY; and\n(B) Applied so that:      \n(1) A HAZARD to EMPLOYEES or other PERSONS is not constituted, (P) and   \n(2) Contamination including toxic residues due to drip, drain, fog, splash or spray on FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES is prevented, and for a RESTRICTED USE PESTICIDE, this is achieved by: (P)      \n(a) Removing the items, (P)   \n(b) Covering the items with impermeable covers, (P) or   \n(c) Taking other appropriate preventive actions, (P) and   \n(d) Cleaning and SANITIZING EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS after the application. (P)  \n(C) A RESTRICTED USE PESTICIDE shall be applied only by an applicator certified as defined in 7 USC 136 Definitions, (e) Certified Applicator, of the Federal Insecticide, Fungicide, and Rodenticide Act, or a PERSON under the direct supervision of a certified applicator. (Pf)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not used according to manufacturer's label instructions","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"and the Reach-in cooler","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Establishment shall provide a clear date marking system."}]},{"inspectionid":"45143","inspectionDate":"2019-02-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"GRILL AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-02-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"and the Reach-in cooler","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-02-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Establishment shall provide a clear date marking system."}]},{"inspectionid":"43205","inspectionDate":"2018-06-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"and the Reach-in cooler","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-06-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Establishment shall provide a clear date marking system."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-06-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"41861","inspectionDate":"2017-09-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"Person-in-charge","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"Person-in-charge","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"Person-in-charge","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-09-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"Person-in-charge","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"Person-in-charge","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-09-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"37509","inspectionDate":"2016-11-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"after handling soiled equipment, surfaces, utensils","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed with hot water and soap for at least 20 seconds after contamination."},{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2016-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4023"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}